BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Internal, 1845-1981, undated; 2
  - Audio-Visual Services, 1971-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Audit Report, 1970-1976 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Aviation Department, 1975-1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - B Cross-Reference Sheets, 1963-1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - “B” Association, 1962-1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - “B” Day, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ball Appreciation Scholarship, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1966-1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Baptist Student Union, 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Baptist Student Union Building, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Bards and Rhapsody in White, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Baseball, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Baylor Band, 1967-1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - “Baylor and Baptist Dollars”, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Baylor Barber Shop, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Bear Club, 1960-1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Book Store, 19-1981 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Books: A List of Acquisitions, 1959-1968 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Calendar, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Challenge, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Baylor Chamber of Commerce, 1960-1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Baylor Christian Community, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Baylor Christian Maturity Council, undated (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1960-1962 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Dentistry, 1976-1980 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1943-1961 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 4), 1969 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 4), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (3 of 4), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine (4 of 4), 1969 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Baylor College of Medicine, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Baylor Day, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Baylor Film, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Baylor Health Club, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Baylor History Collection, 1965-1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Baylor Law Alumni Association, 1965-1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - The Baylor Line, 1960-1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Baylor Mace, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Baylor Medical Alumni Association, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Baylor Nationwide, 1973-1979 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Baylor Parents League, 1971-1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Baylor Press, 1960-1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Baylor Recreation Camp, 1962-1972 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Baylor Religious Hour Choir, 1961-1968 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Baylor Rodeo Club, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Baylor Round Table, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Baylor Round-Up, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Baylor School of Law Foundation, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Baylor-Southwest Texas State Agreement, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Baylor Stadium Corporation, 1950-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Baylor Student Supreme Court, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Baylor Theater, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Baylor University Employee (B.U.E.) Credit Union, 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Baylor University Graduate Division, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Baylor University Hall of Fame, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1967-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1969-1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Baylor University Medical Center (1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Baylor University Medical Center (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Baylor University Medical Center (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Baylor University Medical Center (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Baylor University Medical Center, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Baylor University Medical Center (1 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Baylor University Medical Center (2 of 2), 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Baylor University Nurses Alumnae Association, 1965-1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - B.U. Policy (General), 1974-1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Baylor University Revival, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Baylor University Structure and Statistics, 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - “Bear Downs”, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Bearette Emblem Club, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Bears/Mascot, 1967, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Bicentennial Celebration, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Biology Department, 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Biology Department, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Biology Department, 1975-1981 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Board of Publications, 1961-1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Book of Reports-Christian Education Commission, 1960-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Borden Freshman Prize, 1960-1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Brooks Hall, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Budget Reports and Information [RESTRICTED], 1968-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Building on Campus, 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Burleson Academic Quadrangle, 1967-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Burleson Hall, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Business Office [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Business Office (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Business Office (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Business Office (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Business Office (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Business Office (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Business Office (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1963 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Business Office [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Business Office (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Business Office (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Business Office [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Business Office [RESTRICTED], 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Business and Financial Affairs [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws of Baylor University, 1956-1966 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Bylaws of Baylor University — Proposed Revisions (1 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Bylaws of Baylor University — Proposed Revisions (2 of 2), 1978-1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - C Cross-Reference Sheets, 1962-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Cain Homes, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Calendar Committee, 1966-1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Campus Beautification, 1970-1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Campus Committees, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Campus Planning Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Campus Police, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Campus Services (Security), 1976-1981 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Campus Standards, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - “Campus Study of Baylor University Master Plan,” Prepared by Calhoun, Tungate and Jackson, Architects, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Carroll Science and Carroll Library Restoration, 1969-1980 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Carroll Science Hall, 1966-1969 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Cashier/Credit/National Defense Student Loans (NDSL) [RESTRICTED], 1975-1981 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Castellaw Communications Building, 1962-1977 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Central Services Pricing Policy for University Departments, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Chancellor’s Report, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Chapel, 1959-1962 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Chaplain, 1978-1981 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Charter of Baylor University, 1845-1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Charter of Baylor University, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Chemistry Department, 1960-1977 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry Department, 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - CHIS Service Club, 1965-1970 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Cigarette Machines, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Circle K, 1967-1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Class Attendance Policy, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Classics Department, 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Clifton, John [Hazing Incident] (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Clifton, John [Hazing Incident] (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Clubs, 1967-1976 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1960-1963 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1976-1981 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - “Comer Case” [Contraceptives], 1971 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Commencement, 1960-1967 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1968-1973 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Commencement, 1974-1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1977-1979 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1980-1981 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Charges, 1964-1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Procedure Opinion Poll, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Associate Dean of Arts and Sciences, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Committee on the Elimination of Sex Discrimination, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Experimental Education, 1970-1972 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Committee on General Classroom Building, 1968-1971 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Communications Center, 1959-1960 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Communications Hall of Fame, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Complimentary Tickets, 1970-1980 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Computation Center, 1967-1980 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Computer Committee, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Conservative Society of Baylor University, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Constitution Seminar, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Continuing Education, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Construction Program for Future [Campus Expansion], 1967 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Convocation, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Council for Christian Studies, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Council of Deans, 1973-1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Council of Deans — Meeting Minutes, 1974-1979 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Counseling Center, 1959-1968 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Course Offerings, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Criminal Justice Program, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Cultural Arts Fund, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Cultural Awareness Week, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Curriculum Problems Committee, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Custodial Service, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - D Cross-Reference Sheets, 1967-1978 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Dancing on Campus, 1962-1970 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Data Processing Center, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Dawson Lectures on Church & State, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Dean of Academic Services, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Dean of Admissions, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Dean of the Graduate School, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Dean of Instruction, 1960-1964 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Dean of Instruction, 1965-1967 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Instruction, 1968-1973 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Dean of Men, 1960-1969 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Dean of Students, 1962-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Dean of Students, 1965-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Dean of Women, 1947-1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Demonstration [Vietnam], 1967 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Denominational and Community Relations, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Department Chairmen, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Department of Communication Disorders (Speech Pathology), 1975-1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Department Heads, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Development, 1960-1961 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Development, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Development (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Development (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Development (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Development (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Development, 1970-1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Development, 1977-1981 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Development Council, 1970-1975 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Development Council, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Development Council, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Diadeloso, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Director of Property Management, 1979-1981 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Division Councils, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Dormitories, 1960-1975 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Drama Department, 1959-1963 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Drama Department, 1964-1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Drama Department Resignations and Faculty Statement, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Drill Team, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Duplicating Service, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - E Cross-Reference Sheets, 1967-1977 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Economic Department, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Edgefield Apartments, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Care Units, Baylor Stadium, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Energy Conservation, 1975-1978 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Engineering and Computer Science Department, 1964-1981 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - English Department, 1960-1970 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - English Department, 1971-1972 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - English Department, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - English Department, 1977-1981 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1954-1980 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Studies, 1969-1977 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - European Tours, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Evening Division Program, 1959-1971 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Evolution, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Exchange Students, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board, 1965-1974 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Executive Vice President, 1970-1971 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Executive Vice President (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Executive Vice President (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Executive Vice President and Provost (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Executive Vice President and Provost (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Executive Vice President and Provost/Dean of Facilities (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Executive Vice President and Provost/Dean of Facilities (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Executive Vice President and Dean of Facilities, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Executive Vice President and Dean, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Executive Vice President and Dean, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Executive Vice President and Dean/Chief Operating Officer, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Executive Vice President and Chief Operating Officer (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Executive Vice President and Chief Operating Officer (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Experimental Education, 1971-1974, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Extension Program, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - External Affairs (Development) (1 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - External Affairs (Development) (2 of 2), 1979-1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - F Cross-Reference Sheets, 1963-1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Facilities Planning and Management, 1975-1981 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Faculty, 1959-1962 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Faculty, 1963-1964 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Faculty, 1965-1966 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Faculty, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Faculty, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Faculty, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Faculty, 1972-1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Additions Committee, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Budget Council, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Development Committee, 1969-1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1970-1977 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Fellowships, 1961-1970 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1963-1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Housing, 1962-1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Lounge, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Performance Forms [RESTRICTED], 1967-1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Rating Forms [RESTRICTED], 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Ratings and Evaluation Forms, 1969-1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Retreat, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Senate, 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Far Eastern Educational Exchange Program, 1971-1981 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Festschrift, 1962 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Financial Reports [RESTRICTED], 1959-1965 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reports [RESTRICTED], 1966-1975 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Financial Vice-President, 1960-1975 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Fine Arts, 1960-1981 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Fine Arts Center, 1976-1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Focus Week, 1959-1967 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Football (1 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Football (2 of 2), 1963-1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Football (1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Football (2 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Football (3 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Football, 1969-1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Students, 1961-1971 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Foundations, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Four Cultures Program, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Fraternities and Sororities (1 of 2), 1962-1981 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Fraternities and Sororities (2 of 2), 1962-1981 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - French and Italian Department, 1966-1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - “Friends of the Library”, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Friendship Class [Directory], 1962 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - G Cross-Reference Sheets, 1962-1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - General Counsel, 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Geology Department, 1960-1964 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Geology Department, 1965-1973 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Geology Department, 1974-1981 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - German and Russian Department, 1963-1976 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1958-1961 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Gifts [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Gifts (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Gifts (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Girls Auxiliary Queens Court, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Girl’s Drill Team, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Golden Wave Band, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Government Property, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Grade Inflation Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Grade Study Committee, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Dean and Assistant Vice President, 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Dean and Assistant Vice President, 1978-1981 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Dean Search, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Dean and Vice Provost, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Faculty Library Committee, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Faculty Research Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Office, 1967-1973 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Research Committee, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Research Institute of Baylor University, 1961-1967 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Graduate School, 1958-1960 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School, 1961-1964 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School, 1974-1977 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Grants, 1965-1977 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Green and Gold Football Game, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Grievance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1960-1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Groundbreaking of W. L. Moody Library (Oct. 21, 1966) (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - H Cross-Reference Sheets, 1968-1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1959-1961 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1964-1965 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1967-1969 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1975-1977 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Hankamer School of Business, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Hankamer School of Business, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Harris House, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Hazing, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Administration, 1969-1976 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Health Center, 1965-1980 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Heating Plant, 1961-1969 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Heritage Campaign, 1974-1979 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Heritage Club, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - History Department, 1960-1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - History Department, 1975-1981 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Holidays/Holiday Schedule, 1962-1966 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Homecoming, 1964-1978 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Home Economics, 1966-1981 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Honor Code and System, 1968-1977, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Honor Council [RESTRICTED], 1960-1978 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Honor Council [RESTRICTED], 1979-1981 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1960-1961 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1962-1964 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1967-1968 (Box 50, Folder 4)